<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Krishna Bhandari</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Krishna Bhandari</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:21:27 +0545</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes we overcomplicate things</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sometime-we-overcomplicate-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:21:27 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sometime-we-overcomplicate-things/</guid>
      <description>How I overthink something and made the complex implementation and later realized that we can handle it in a better and simpler way. I was dealing with the form using Vue 3 and that form needs to be repeated once we click the add new button. First, I thought of creating a parent component called Question and inside that, it will consist of a QuestionItem component which we can use to loop for the repeater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Vue3: A Step-by-Step Guide to Using vue-router for Page Redirection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mastering-vue3-a-step-by-step-guide-to-using-vue-router-for-page-redirection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 17:21:27 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mastering-vue3-a-step-by-step-guide-to-using-vue-router-for-page-redirection/</guid>
      <description>First of all we need to import the function called useRouter from the vue-router plugin&#xA;import { useRouter} from &amp;#39;vue-router&amp;#39;; The useRouter function provides us with a convenient way to access the Vue router instance and perform redirects to different pages. Let&amp;rsquo;s assign the result of useRouter function to the constant called router&#xA;const router = useRouter(); Finally, we can use this router to navigate between pages. Example:&#xA;const handleSubmit = () =&amp;gt; { axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Vue 3 template refs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-vue-3-template-refs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 17:21:27 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-use-vue-3-template-refs/</guid>
      <description>After working with Vue 2 refs and switching to Vue 3 refs can be tricky for the first time as we do not have access to this.$refs in Vue3&#xA;Problem: Recently, I was working on Vue 3 project and using VeeValidate for client-side form validation. I was also using the bootstrap modal for the form. Now, I need to reset the form when someone clicks on add/edit button. There is resetForm method available on the VeeValidate Form component so we need to get the form and call resetForm method.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
